Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audio Lab materials, 1962 -- 2003; UA136.004; 8.4 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Why Economic Reforms Won't Work, given by Marshall Goldman, 1989-03-15; UA136.004.028.00032; Goldman, Marshall (Case 28)
  - Interntional Business - Global Responsibility, given by C. Joseph Labonté, 1989-05; UA136.004.028.00033; Labonté, C. Joseph (Case 28)
    CEO, Reebok
  - Prof. Gross Memorial, 1990-12-03; UA136.004.028.00034 (Case 28)
  - Lecture given by the Canadian Ambassador to the U.N. Security Council, 1991-04-17; UA136.004.028.00035 (Case 28)
  - Fransis Adams Lecture, given by Ambassador Maynard Glitman, 1991-09-26; UA136.004.028.00036; Glitman, Maynard (Case 28)
  - A Global Partnership - U.S. and Germany, given by Hans Dietrick Genscher, 1993-04-28; UA136.004.028.00037; Genscher, Hans Dietrick (Case 28)
    Fletcher School lecture
  - Melodic and Poetic Design in Troubadour Lyric, given by Vincent Pollina, 1994-03-30; UA136.004.028.00038; Pollina, Vincent (Case 28)
    Olin Center lecture
  - Dr. Claude Bernard and Emile Zola, given by Seymour Simches and Dr. Cremone, 1994-04-12; UA136.004.028.00039; Simches, Seymour (Case 28)
  - Child Nutrition: The Critical Link to Achieve America's Health and Education Goals, given by Surgeon General M. Joycelyn Elders, M.D., 1994-06-27; UA136.004.028.00040; Elders, M. Joycelyn (Case 28)
  - Europe and the Middle East: The Future of Democracy, given by Margaret Thatcher, 1997-09-24; UA136.004.028.00041; Thatcher, Margaret (Case 29, Case 28)
    Former Prime Minister of Great Britain. 1997 Isaam Fares Lecture
    videocassettes; audiocassettes
  - Europe and the Middle East: The Future of Democracy program, 1997-09-24; UA136.004.028.00042 (Case 28)
  - The Woman Writer as Phoenix: Goerge Sand, Biography, and the Death of the Author, given by Isabelle Naginski, 1998-04-22; UA136.004.028.00043; Naginski, Isabelle (Case 28)
  - Peter Jennings at Tufts, 1988-03-03; UA136.004.029.00001; Jennings, Peter (Case 29)
    videocassettes
  - Video Tour of Tufts, E. Dente, 1988-06-03; UA136.004.029.00002 (Case 29)
  - Seminar on US-Soviet Economic Relations after the Moscow Summit (Panel #1), The Fletcher School, 1988-06-20; UA136.004.029.00003 (Case 29)
  - Seminar on US-Soviet Economic Relations after the Moscow Summit (Panel #2), The Fletcher School, 1988-06-20; UA136.004.029.00004 (Case 29)
  - Belize: The Caribbean Nation in the Heart of Central America, given by Manuel Esquivel, 1988-10-03; UA136.004.029.00005; Esquivel, Manuel (Case 29)
    Prime Minister of Belize
  - Going It Alone? The Course of American Diplomacy Fletcher School conference, 1988-10-27; UA136.004.029.00006; Henrikson, Alan (Case 29)
  - German Expressionism, given by Sol Gittleman, 1989-02-02; UA136.004.029.00007; Gittleman, Sol, 1934- (Case 29)
  - Development, Deforestation, and Biodiversity: A Question of Balance? keynote address, 1989-02-22; UA136.004.029.00008 (Case 29)
  - Development, Deforestation, and Biodiversity: A Question of Balance? panel discussion, 1989-02-22; UA136.004.029.00009 (Case 29)
  - The Development of French Society through Comedy and Satire, given by Seymour Simches, 1989-03-07; UA136.004.029.00010; Simches, Seymour (Case 29)
  - Lecture given by John Rassias, 1989-05-02; UA136.004.030.00001; Rassias, John (Box 30)
  - Fletcher School Commencement, 1989-05-21; UA136.004.030.00002 (Box 30)
    Address: Provost Sol Gittleman
  - Lecture given by Miguel Aleman, 1989-10-17; UA136.004.030.00003; Aleman, Miguel (Box 30)
    Ambassador from Mexico
  - Lecture given by Jeanne Dillon, 1990-03-27; UA136.004.030.00004; Dillon, Jeanne (Box 30)
    Video tape of class at Wessell Library
  - Interative Video Presentation - A la recontre de Phillippe, given by Gilberte Furstenberg, 1990-12-10; UA136.004.030.00005; Furstenberg, Gilberte (Box 30)
  - Fletcher Follies - The Video, 1991-04-05; UA136.004.030.00006 (Box 30)
  - Fletcher School Graduation Ceremony, 1991-05-12; UA136.004.030.00007 (Box 30)
  - Fletcher School event featuring Jean-Baptiste Aristide and Jonathan Demme, 1992; UA136.004.030.00008; Aristide, Jean-Baptiste; Demme, Jonathan (Box 30)
  - Fletcher School Commencement, 1992-05-17; UA136.004.030.00009 (Box 30)
  - TAB Wall Painting, 1992-06-29; UA136.004.030.00010 (Box 30)
  - Lecture given by Haruki Murakami, 1994; UA136.004.030.00011; Murakami, Haruki (Box 30)
  - Tufts-SCAT Interactive Program: Immigration, given by Sol Gittleman, 1994-05-23; UA136.004.030.00012; Gittleman, Sol, 1934- (Box 30)
  - Lecture given by Marvin Minsky, 1995-02-22; UA136.004.030.00013; Minsky, Marvin (Box 30)
  - Hot Wars, Cold Wars, and Culture Wars: American Journalism and the Ancient Greeks, given by Jennifer Roberts, 1995-10-16; UA136.004.030.00014; Roberts, Jennifer (Box 30)
  - Lecture given by Nazli Kibria, 1996-01-19; UA136.004.030.00015; Kibria, Nazli (Box 30)
  - Lecture given by Soheir Morsey, 1996-01-22; UA136.004.030.00016; Morsey, Soheir (Box 30)
  - Lecture given Hiedi Tinsman, 1996-01-26; UA136.004.030.00017; Tinsman, Hiedi (Box 30)
  - Lecture given by Rao Brinda, 1996-01-29; UA136.004.030.00018; Brinda, Rao (Box 30)
  - Howard Hunter Retirement Reception, 1997-12-01; UA136.004.030.00019 (Box 30)
  - Sol's Reception, 2002-06-05; UA136.004.030.00020; Gittleman, Sol, 1934- (Box 30)
  - Seymour Simches: A Mentor for Tufts, 2003; UA136.004.030.00021 (Box 30)
    videocassettes; videocassettes
  - Segregation in Boston and Schools, 1974-09-25; UA136.004.030.00022 (Box 30)
- University audiovisual materials, 1968 -- 2007; UA136.005; 56.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains the unprocessed material that was previously in the UAV collection and unable to be incorporated into any other collection.
  This series is not processed
  - Audio and video recordings, UAV-001 (Box 1)
    Former barcode 39090011485162g.
  - Audio and video recordings, UAV-002 (Box 2)
    Former barcode 39090011485170g
  - Audio and video recordings, UAV-003 (Box 3)
    Former barcode 39090011485188g.
  - Audio and video recordings, UAV-004 (Box 4)
    Former barcode 39090011485196g.
  - Audio and video recordings, UAV-005 (Box 5)
    Former barcode 39090011485204g.
  - Audio and video recordings - 16" records, UAV-006 (Box 6)
    Former barcode 39090011485212g.
  - Audio and video recordings, UAV-007 (Box 7)
    Former barcode 39090011485220g.
  - Audio and video recordings, UAV-008 (Box 8)
    Former barcode 39090011485238g
  - Audio Tape, UAV-009 (Box 9)
    Former barcode 39090011486582g.
  - Audio and Cassette Tapes, UAV-010 (Box 10)
    Former barcode 39090011486590g.
  - Audio and Cassette Tapes, UAV-011 (Box 11)
    Former barcode 39090011486608g.
  - 16mm Film, UAV-012 (Box 12)
    Former barcode 39090011486616g
  - VHS, UAV-013 (Box 13)
    Includes VHS tape of "How One College Educates" written by Grant F. Curtis and William P. Saunders, photographed and directed by William P. Saunders; also includes footage which according to the tape is "The following social activities at the Delta Upsilon House filmed by David [A'62] and Linda Adzigian [J'62] during the 1961-1962 school year, and include most of the brothers from the classes of 1962-1965, our dates, our chaperones, and the legendary Sam Sardone. Former barcode 39090011486624gHighlights in order of appearance: -Campus Scenes -1961 Rush Activities -Chi Omega singers in living room -Beatnik Party -Brief Shot of Mrs. Leonard -Playboy Party -Chorus line singing "Fever" -Christmas Formal -St. Patrick's Party and green potato salad -Hell Week -The Original Hawaiian Party -Spring Weekend at the Seacrest -Graduation Class of 1962
  - 16mm Film, UAV-014 (Box 14)
    Former barcode 39090011486632g.
  - Video recordings, UAV-015 (Box 15)
    Includes VHS of news segment from Action News 5:30 WTNH 8 New Haven/Hartford, CT on The Tufts Beelzebubs as part of Alumnae Relations Project called the "Great Tuftonian Train Ride" in April of 1989 where the Beelzebubs performed at train stations from Washinton D.C. to Boston. Includes VHS tape "How one college educates," possibly a copy made by Admissions Office in 1992 (see card catalog). Former barcode 39090011488182g.
  - Phonograph recordings, UAV-016 (Box 16)
    Four copies of the Odikon Singers 1951 recording. Former barcode 39090011488307g.
  - KC Visuals tapes-Medical School Commencement, 1996; UAV-017 (Box 17)
    analog AV media Former barcode 39090014015958g
  - KC Visuals tapes-VHS tapes, 1995 -- 2002; UAV-018 (Box 18)
    analog AV media former barcode 39090014015966g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Beelzabubs tapes and trains, 1989 -- 1994; UAV-019 (Box 19)
    analog AV media Former barcode 39090014015974g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Tufts campus and commencement, 1991 -- 2001; UAV-020 (Box 20)
    analog AV media Former barcode 39090014015982g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Betty Bao Lord, various footage, 1991 -- 1992; UAV-021 (Box 21)
    analog AV media Former barcode 39090014015990g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Beelzebubs, 1989; UAV-022 (Box 22)
    analog AV media Former barcode 39090014016006g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Athletics, 1980 -- 2004; UAV-023 (Box 23)
    analog AV media Date range is approximate. 9 KCS20 tapes, 4 MBR tapes, 4 UCA20s tapes, 2 audio cassettes, 1 vhs tape; former barcode 39090014025189g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Commencement, Beelzebubs, and basketball, 1988 -- 2002; UAV-024 (Box 24)
    analog AV media 10 KCA60 tapes, 4 KCS20 tapes, 1 MBR tape, 3 VHS tapes; former barcode 39090014025197g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Commencement events, 2003 -- 2007; UAV-025 (Box 25)
    analog AV media --electronic media 4 audio cassettes, 10 Mini DVs, 5 Ampex tapes, 1 KCA60 tape, 30 DVDs; former barcode 39090014025205g
  - Mac floppy disk, 1995; UAV-026 (Box 26)
    analog AV media --electronic media The date is approximate. Found uncataloged and unlabeled in AC boxes relating to exhibit '5000 years of recorded human history'. former barcode 39090014025452g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Aidekman Art Center construction and football, 1968 -- 1991; UAV-027 (Box 27)
    analog AV media --electronic media 4 KCA60, 8 KCS20, 1 Ampex 197 [10 relating to Aidekman Art Center construction and 3 relating to football]; former barcode 39090014026195g
  - KC Visuals tapes-1995 and 1998 commencement, 1995 -- 1998; UAV-028 (Box 28)
    analog AV media --electronic media 5 KCA60 and 5 MBR60; former barcode 39090014026203g
  - KC Visuals tapes-MacJannet, 2001 Distinguished achievement, 1990 -- 2001; UAV-029 (Box 29)
    analog AV media --electronic media 4 KCA60, 2 Ampex 197, 5 KCS20, 1 MBR60, 2 VHS, 4 audio; former barcode 39090014026211g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Commencement events, Bubs, Dental events, 1989 -- 1997; UAV-050 (Box 30)
    analog AV media --electronic media 8 MBR 60 and KCA 60 tapes, 20 KCS20 tapes, and 11 VHS tapes. former barcode 39090015515824g
  - KC Visuals tapes-Commencement events, Bubs, Dental events, 1989 -- 2006; UAV-051 (Box 31)
    analog AV media --electronic media 2 KCA 30 tapes, 3 KCA 60 and MBR60 tapes, 1 UCA tape, 1 KCS20 tape, 3 VHS, 2 DVCAM 124 tapes, 4 DVCAM 184 tapes, 11 mini DVM60 tapes.; former barcode 39090015515832g
  - VHS, UAV-070 (Box 32)
    analog AV media Former barcode 39090011484389g.
  - VHS, UAV-071 (Box 33)
    analog AV media Former barcode 39090011484397g.
  - "How One College Educates," 16mm film, UA136.002730 (Box 34)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    See UAV-013 (box 13) for access copy on VHS.
- Additional accessions, UA136.002727
  - Tufts Seal, Inaugurations and Convocations Programs, Honor Roll of the Great War, Tufts College: Ballou Hall and Chapel Plate, 1855 -- 1953; UA136-001 (Box 1)
  - College Seal, UA136-002 (Box 2)
  - Historical clippings and reports, UA136-003 (Box 3)
  - Historical materials, UA136-004 (Box 4)
  - Historical materials, duplicate photos, UA136-005 (Box 5)
  - Historical materials, photographs, UA136-006 (Box 6)
  - Microfilm: Meeting minutes for faculty, Trustees, Trustee Committees, BSOT, and Personnel files., UA136-007 (Box 7)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Microfilm:Publications 1, UA136-009 (Box 8)
  - Microfilm:Publications 2, UA136-011 (Box 9)
  - Microfilm:Archives, UA136-015 (Box 10)
  - Russell Miller Files, UA136-016 (Box 11)
  - Brochures, 1958 -- 1969; UA136-017 (Box 12)
  - Framed print of Goddard Gymnasium, 1892; UA136-018 (Box Shared 13)
  - Framed print Packard Hall/Library, UA136-019 (Box Shared 13)
  - Framed print of Eaton, Goddard, Miner and Paige Halls, UA136-020 (Box Shared 13)
  - Framed print of Goddard Chapel, East, Packard and West Halls, UA136-021 (Box Shared 13)
  - Audio Lab-reel to reel and video, UA136-029 (Box 13)
    This box contains tapes of an unknown nature that were stored and accessioned alongside Audio Lab recordings of Tufts lectures and performances.
  - Audio Lab-reel to reel and video, UA136-032 (Box 14)
    This box contains tapes of an unknown nature that were stored and accessioned alongside Audio Lab recordings of Tufts lectures and performances
  - Mayoralty film reel, 1953; UA136-034 (Box 15)
  - Media Center reels, 1970 -- 1980; UA136-035 (Box 16)
    Box inventory created by Tim Walsh in 2013 lives in Q/collection documentation.
  - Media Center reels and cassettes, 1965 -- 1980; UA136-036 (Box 17)
  - Media Center reels, 1965 -- 1980; UA136-037 (Box 18)
  - Media Center reels, 1965 -- 1980; UA136-038 (Box 19)
  - Media Center reels and cassettes, 1965 -- 1995; UA136-039 (Box 20)
  - Media Center reels, 1965 -- 1980; UA136-040 (Box 21)
  - Media Center reels, 1965 -- 1980; UA136-041 (Box 22)
  - Media Center VHS tapes, 1990 -- 1995; UA136-042 (Box 23)
  - Media Center VHS tapes, 1985 -- 1995; UA136-043 (Box 24)
  - Media Center VHS tapes, 1985 -- 1995; UA136-044 (Box 25)
  - Media Center VHS tapes, 1980 -- 1995; UA136-045 (Box 26)
  - Media Center VHS tapes, 1980 -- 1995; UA136-046 (Box 27)
  - Media Center VHS tapes and broadcast videocassettes, 1985 -- 1995; UA136-047 (Box 28)
  - Media Center VHS tapes and broadcast videocassettes, 1985 -- 1995; UA136-048 (Box 29)
  - Media Center VHS tapes and broadcast videocassettes, 1985 -- 1995; UA136-049 (Box 30)
  - Media Center VHS tapes and broadcast videocassettes, 1985 -- 1995; UA136-050 (Box 31)
  - Media Center broadcast videocassettes, 1960 -- 1985; UA136-051 (Box 32)
  - Media Center Tufts Promotional Film Reel, 1950; UA136-052 (Box 33)